gethucinema.com 2016-10-02

# Privacy Policy | Gethu Cinema

**Gethu Cinema** ** ** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, mobile site.

**Information Automatically Logged  **

Your demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

**Cookies**  
Various methods are employed to gather this data. “Cookies” are used to distinguish and relate non personal data to individuals. These are “small strings of text” that are stored in browsers; cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so.

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your login information so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

Demographic and profile data is collected at our site.

This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This data is also used to serve banner ads.

**Advertisers**

We work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information. ** **

**Registration Forms**  
Gethu Cinema does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals, except when individuals provide such information on a voluntary basis in our Registration Forms

Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. Contact information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.

**External Links**

This site contains links to other sites.  **Gethu Cinema  **is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**  
Public Forums**

This site makes chat rooms, opinion polls, Comments and/or news available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**  
Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to maintain quality of service and prevent misuse.

BUSINESS TRANSFERS

If Gethu Cinema, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Gethu Cinema goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Gethu Cinema may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Felix may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Felix’s sole discretion. Felix encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.

C **ontacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us](http://www.gethucinema.com/contact).
